Class of 1934 Records, 1927-1994
Smith College Archives
Class of 1934 Records
1927-1994
Smith College. Class of 1934.
RG 80
17 boxes (9.8 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1934.
Historical Note
The Class of 1934 was the fifty-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1934 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1934, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1934 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Alumnae Council Reports 1940-1943, 1960-1972, 1975, 1990 (Box 2052, Folder 1)
- Alumnae News 1955-1970 (Box 2052, Folder 2)
- Books Given by Class or Class Members n.d. (Box 2052, Folder 3)
- Book Memorials for Deceased Class Members 1939-1959 (Box 2052, Folder 4)
- Christmas Vespers 1933 (Box 2052, Folder 5)
- Commencement 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 6)
- Commencement Music 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 7)
- Commencement Photographs 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 8)
- Commencement Speaker 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 9)
- Correspondence 1938-1984 (Box 2052, Folder 10)
- Deceased Class Members 1960-1968 (Box 2052, Folder 11)
- Financial 1954-1974 (Box 2052, Folder 12)
- Financial Documents 1959-1979 (Box 2052, Folder 13)
- Freshman Frolic 1930 (Box 2052, Folder 14)
- Freshman Handbook 1930-1931 (Box 2052, Folder 15)
- Fund Agent 1957-1964 (Box 2052, Folder 16)
- Groups 1930-1934 (Box 2052, Folder 17)
- Ivy Day 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 18)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 19)
- Junior Prom 1933 (Box 2052, Folder 20)
- Junior Prom-Garden Party 1933 (Box 2052, Folder 21)
- Junior Ushers 1933 (Box 2052, Folder 22)
- Junior Year Abroad Program 1932-1933 (Box 2052, Folder 23)
- Last Chapel 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 24)
- Class Letters 1936-1949 (Box 2052, Folder 25)
- Class Letters 1950-1959 (Box 2052, Folder 26)
- Class Letters 1960-1969 (Box 2052, Folder 27)
- Class Letters 1970-1979 (Box 2052, Folder 28)
- Class Letters 1981-1989 (Box 2052, Folder 29)
- Class Letters 1990- (Box 2052, Folder 30)
- Lost Class Members 1957-1974 (Box 2052, Folder 31)
- Minutes and Reports 1939-1989 (Box 2052, Folder 32)
- Class Officers 1961, 1989 (Box 2052, Folder 33)
- Class Officers' Correspondence 1975-1980, 1992 (Box 2052, Folder 34)
- Rally Day 1932 (Box 2052, Folder 35)
- Reunions-Class Reunion Handbook n.d. (Box 2053, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1935 (Box 2053, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1939 (Box 2053, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1944 (Box 2053, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1949 (Box 2053, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1954 (Box 2053, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 2053, Folder 7)
- Reunions-Correspondence/Preparations 1959 (Box 2053, Folder 8)
- Reunions-Correspondence/Preparations 1959 (Box 2053, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1964 (Box 2053, Folder 10)
- Reunions-Correspondence/Preparations 1964 (Box 2053, Folder 11)
- Reunions-Correspondence/Preparations 1964 (Box 2053, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1969 (Box 2053.1, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1974 (Box 2053.1, Folder 2)
- Reunions-Preparations 1974 (Box 2053.1, Folder 3)
- Reunions-Photo Album 1974 (Box 2053.1, Folder 4)
- Reunions-Special Gift 1974 (Box 2053.1, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1979 (Box 2053.1, Folder 6)
- Reunions-Preparations 1979 (Box 2053.1, Folder 7)
- Reunions-Post-reunion Correspondence 1979 (Box 2053.1, Folder 8)
- Reunions-Scrapbook 1979 (Box 2053.2, Folder 1)
- Reunions-Scrapbook 1979 (Box 2053.2, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1984 (Box 2053.2, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1989 (Box 2053.2, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1992 (Box 2053.2, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1994 (Box 2053.2, Folder 6)
- Reunions n.d. (Box 2053.2, Folder 7)
- Songs 1934 (Box 2053.2, Folder 8)
- Sophomore Carnival 1932 (Box 2053.2, Folder 9)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1932 (Box 2053.2, Folder 10)
- Step Sings 1934 (Box 2053.2, Folder 11)
- Class Supper 1934 (Box 2053.2, Folder 12)
- Senior Dramatics 1934 (Box 2054, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics-Music 1934 (Box 2054, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs, Individuals 1934 (Box 2054, Folder 3)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs, Groups 1934 (Box 2054, Folder 4)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs, Groups 1934 (Box 2054, Folder 5)
- Senior Dramatics-Sikelianos Bibliography 1934 (Box 2055, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics-Sikelianos Correspondence 1934 (Box 2055, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics-Sikelianos Photographs 1934 (Box 2055, Folder 3)
- Senior Dramatics-Sikelianos Publications and Clippings 1927-1952 (Box 2055, Folder 4)
- Delphic Festival 1927 (Box 2055, Folder 5)
- Works by A. Sikelianos: Athene Magazine (Box 2055, Folder 6)
- Works by A. Sikelianos: The Death of Digenis (Box 2055, Folder 7)
- Works by A. Sikelianos: Mater Dei (Box 2055, Folder 8)
- Works by A. Sikelianos: Various Works (Box 2055, Folder 9)
- Reunion Scrapbooks (Box OV)